westsiderentals.com 2010-01-18

# Apartment Rentals in Los Angeles, Orange County and San Diego

## WestsideRentals.com Privacy Policy Statement

**WestsideRentals.com is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of WestsideRentals.com. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.**

### This policy will let you know:

  * What personally identifiable information is collected from you
  * What cookies are and how they are used
  * How your information is used
  * Who is collecting your information
  * With whom your information may be shared
  * What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information
  * How you can access, update or delete your information
  * The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information
  * What else you should know about your online privacy

* * *

### What personally identifiable information is collected from you

The WestsideRentals.com collects information in several ways from different parts of our web site. 

Some personal information is gathered when you register. During registration, we ask for your name and email address. The system will also ask for your street address, city, state/province, zip/postal code, country, and telephone number, although only fields that are marked with an asterisk (*) on the registration field are required. This information is used solely to assist you in navigating the system by automatically filling in certain forms (such as the Vacancy posting form) with your information so that you don't have to continually re-enter it. Once you register you are no longer anonymous to WestsideRentals.com - you have a username and are able to take full advantage of the many offerings of WestsideRentals.com. 

In addition to registration we may ask you for personal information at other times, including (but not limited to) when you place vacancies or take advantage of the other features of WestsideRentals.com. If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence. Every page within the WestsideRentals.com includes a link to this Privacy Policy. 

Back to Top

* * *

### What cookies are and how they are used

As part of offering and providing customizable and personalized services, WestsideRentals.com may use cookies to store and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. Several features of the WestsideRentals.com require that you accept cookies in order to work properly. (See "What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information" for more information on cookies.) 

Generally, we use cookies for the following purposes: 

  * To identify and label all "new" vacancies since your last visit to the site.
  * Optionally to permanently save your password on your computer so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.
  * To enable you to "checklist and compare" vacancies that you want to mark for future retrieval and viewing.

Advertising networks that advertise on WestsideRentals.com may also use their own cookies. 

The WestsideRentals.com may also collect IP addresses for system administration, fraud prevention, and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. 

Back to Top

* * *

### How your information is used

The primary goal of WestsideRentals.com in collecting personal information is to provide you, the user, with a customized experience and to assist your navigation throughout WestsideRentals.com. 

Back to Top

* * *

### Who is collecting your information

When you are asked for personal information on WestsideRentals.com, you are sharing that information with WestsideRentals.com alone, unless it is specifically stated otherwise. However, some activities will, by their very nature, result in your personal information being revealed to other users of the WestsideRentals.com. For example, when you enter personal information on the Vacancy posting form, this information will generally be included in your Vacancy, unless specifically stated otherwise. Also, if you request to be contacted by one of our advertising partners, some of your contact information may be shared. 

Back to Top

* * *

### With whom your information may be shared

As a general rule, WestsideRentals.com will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information except when we have your permission or under special circumstances, such as when we believe in good faith that the law requires it or under the circumstances described below. Please see the Terms of Service or Use Agreements for each of our products and services for more detailed information about how your personal information may be shared. 

WestsideRentals.com may disclose account information in special cases when we have reason to believe that disclosing this information is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be violating the Terms of Service of the WestsideRentals.com or may be causing injury to or interference with (either intentionally or unintentionally) the rights or property of WestsideRentals.com, other users of the WestsideRentals.com, or anyone else that could be harmed by such activities. WestsideRentals.com may disclose or access account information when we believe in good faith that the law requires it and for administrative and other purposes that we deem necessary to maintain, service, and improve our products and services. 

Back to Top

* * *

### What choices are available to you regarding collection, use, and distribution of your information

If you choose not to register or provide personal information, you can still use most of the WestsideRentals.com, but you will not be able to access areas or use features that require registration. 

You also have choices with respect to cookies. By modifying your browser preferences, you have the choice to accept all cookies, to be notified when a cookie is set, or to reject all cookies. If you choose to reject all cookies you will be unable to use those services and features of WestsideRentals.com that require registration in order to participate. These services include the identification of new vacancies that have been posted since your last visit, auto-filling of the logon form, and the clipboard feature. You can still use most of the features of WestsideRentals.com even if you do not accept cookies. 

Back to Top

* * *

### How you can access, update or delete your information

We will provide you with the means to ensure that your personal information is correct and current. You may edit or delete your user profile at any time by clicking on the "My Profile" link or graphic provided by the system once you are logged in. Once you have logged onto the system during a given session, wherever you go on the WestsideRentals.com, your information will stay with you until or unless you click on the "Logoff" link, which is accessible from within the "My Account" screen. 

If you are a previously registered user and you have lost or forgotten your password, you may obtain it by email by using our "Forgot Password" feature. Click the button on any login page to request that your password be emailed to you. We cannot provide your password by any other means. 

Your WestsideRentals.com account can be deleted, but doing so will result in not being able to access any of the features of the program that require user registration. 

Back to Top

* * *

### The kind of security precautions that are in place to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information

Other than the administrator of WestsideRentals.com or other authorized personnel of WestsideRentals.com, you are the only person who has access to your personal information. Your user registration is password-protected to prevent unauthorized access. 

We recommend that you do not divulge your password to anyone. WestsideRentals.com will never ask you for your password in an unsolicited phone call or in an unsolicited email. As an extra security precaution, you may want to logoff once you have completed a session in the WestsideRentals.com. This is to ensure that others cannot access your personal information and correspondence if you share a computer with someone else or are using a computer in a public place like a library or Internet cafe. 

Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, WestsideRentals.com cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online services, and you do so at your own risk. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems. 

Back to Top

* * *

### What else you should know about your online privacy

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online - for example in vacancies that you post or through email - that information can be collected and used by others. In short, if you post personal information online that is accessible to the public, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return. 

Ultimately, you are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of your passwords and/or any account information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you're online. 

Back to Top
